对于像我一样习惯于使用桌面窗口开发的人来说
A platform which terminates apps on its own is a pretty radical departure for
平台自己终止应用是一个很大的改变
anyone like me who cut their teeth on desktop Winforms development.
如果你有相似的开发背景
If you come from a similar background you probably have
你很可能已经能很好的理解生命周期的事件处理是用来干什么的了
a pretty good idea of what to expect in terms of lifecycle event handles.
你通过onCreate函数创建你的用户界面
You start with the onCreate call back where you build and wire up your UI.
一旦界面被创建好  你的Activity也就随之被创建成功了  不难理解
to you that there are also event handlers for when the activity becomes visible.
当Activity能够被看见的时候  会有事件被触发
Once that's done, your activity has been created. It likely won't be a surprise
这个就是开始onStart过程  另一个是  当被切换到这个Activity  处于前台运行状态的时候
Which is onStart and another for when it gets focus and becomes the active
此时是恢复onResume过程  当结束的时候  过程是反过来的
[SOUND] onPause indicates that the activity has lost focus, followed by
暂停onPause过程表示Activity失去了焦点  然后接下来
foreground app, which is onResume. That same sequence, then happens in reverse.
是停止onStop过程  此时Activity就不可见了  最后是销毁onDestroy过程
onStop when the app is no longer visible. Finally, there's an onDestroy method,
生命周期结束  当你的应用程序第一次启动时
indicating the end of the app lifecycle. When your app is first launched, you'll
你会非常快速的经历建立onCreate开始  onStart恢复  onResume这三个过程
quickly move through these states. Create, Start, Resume, one after the other
但是  在这个应用程序的生命周期中  从程序调用创建onCreate
But within the full application lifetime, from when onCreate is first called and
到最后程序结束  Activity的活跃生命周期和
till the app is finally terminated. It will move through the active lifetime and
可视生命周期过程会反复调用很多次  让我们仔细的分析一下
the physical lifetime, many times. Let's look at those in a little more detail.